In this American English pronunciation video,
在这段美式英语发音视频中，
we're going to learn how to pronounce the OW as in NOW diphthong.
我们将学习如何发音像“NOW”中的OW双元音。
Diphthongs are a combination of two sounds,
双元音是两个音的组合，
so they have a starting position and an ending position.
所以它们有一个起始位置和一个结束位置。
To start this sound, drop the jaw.
要开始这个音，放松下巴。
The first sound is similar to the AA as in BAT vowel.
第一个音类似于“BAT”中的AA元音。
The tongue is wide and flat.
舌头宽而平。
The back stretches up a little bit.
舌头的后部稍微向上伸展。
The tongue tip touches the back of the bottom front teeth.
舌尖触碰下前牙的后面。
The upper lip might lift a little,
上唇可能会稍微抬起，
or it will be relaxed.
或者保持放松。
To transition into the second position,
要过渡到第二个位置，
the lips round and the jaw drops less.
嘴唇圆起，下巴下降得少一些。
The back of the tongue stretches up more.
舌头的后部伸展得更多。
This second position is considered the same as the UH as in PUSH vowel.
这个第二个位置被认为与“PUSH”中的UH元音相同。
But when it's a part of a diphthong,
但当它是双元音的一部分时，
the lips round more than when it occurs as a pure vowel.
嘴唇比作为纯元音时更圆。
Let's see this sound up close and in slow motion.
让我们近距离慢动作看看这个音。
Jaw drops.
下巴下降。
Here, the upper lip pulls a little bit.
这里，上唇稍微拉起。
The tongue lifts in the back.
舌头在后部抬起。
Now the lips come in and round as the jaw comes up.
现在嘴唇收拢并圆起，同时下巴抬起。
The word WOUND.
单词“WOUND”。
The lips start in a tight circle for the W,
嘴唇在发W音时开始是一个紧的圆圈，
but then open out for the first position of the diphthong,
但随后为双元音的第一个位置打开，
before rounding again for the second position of the diphthong.
然后再次为双元音的第二个位置圆起。
In a stressed syllable,
在重读音节中，
the OW diphthong curves up, then down.
OW双元音先上升，然后下降。
WOUND.
WOUND。
OW.
OW。
In an unstressed syllable,
在非重读音节中，
it's lower and flatter in pitch,
音调更低更平，
as well as quieter and quicker.
而且更安静更快。
OW, OW.
OW，OW。
The diphthong is unstressed in the word SHUTDOWN.
在单词“SHUTDOWN”中，双元音是非重读的。
OW.
OW。
Let's take a look at this word.
让我们看看这个单词。
Jaw drops, but notice the top lip is relaxed.
下巴下降，但注意上唇是放松的。
It doesn't pull up.
它没有拉起。
Tongue is lifted in the back.
舌头在后部抬起。
In the ending position,
在结束位置，
the lips aren't quite as rounded as they were in the stressed version of this diphthong.
嘴唇不像这个双元音的重读版本那样圆。
Here you see the jaw drop in the first position of the diphthong,
这里你看到双元音的第一个位置下巴下降，
stressed version on top.
重读版本在上面。
Notice that the jaw doesn't drop as much for the unstressed diphthong.
注意非重读双元音下巴没有下降那么多。
Here's the second position.
这是第二个位置。
The lips don't round as much for the unstressed diphthong.
非重读双元音嘴唇没有那么圆。
They're more relaxed.
它们更放松。
Generally,
通常，
the unstressed version of a vowel or diphthong is more relaxed,
非重读版本的元音或双元音更放松，
and often doesn't take the full mouth position.
而且通常不需要完整的口腔位置。
In this case, less jaw drop, and less lip rounding.
在这种情况下，下巴下降得少，嘴唇圆起得少。
This is because we don't take as much time with unstressed syllables.
这是因为我们在非重读音节上花费的时间不多。
They're shorter, so we simplify the mouth movements.
它们更短，所以我们简化了口腔动作。
The OW diphthong, stressed.
OW双元音，重读。
WOUND.
WOUND。
OW.
OW。
Unstressed.
非重读。
Shut down.
OW.
OW。
OW,
OW，
OW.
OW。
OW,
OW，
OW.
OW。
Example words.
例词。
Repeat with me.
跟我重复。
About.
OW.
OW。
About.
Sound.
OW.
OW。
Sound.
House.
OW.
OW。
House.
Let down.
OW.
OW。
Let down.
Blackout.
OW.
OW。
Blackout.
Found.
OW.
OW。
Found.